Encoded By " Pirata-Tuga " ... TuGAZx ... Enjoy it !
Shutter
Cheers !
Excellent .
Let 's drink until we drop .
Save something for your wife .
Are you kidding ?
Alcohol revives me .
The later it gets , the hornier I get .
Another glass . A little sip .
Tell me , Jane ...
What year are you in ?
4th year .
A senior should know better .
What are you doing with Tun ?
He 's a hunk .
You keep saying that .
Making Jim ask for girl 's numbers .
Then breaking their hearts .
Speaking of broken hearts ...
Remember the time ...
that girl left him a drunken mess .
Her name was Kay .
Ignore them .
Wait . I have a question .
How can a guy like you get married ?
What 's wrong with me ?
After a long tiring day ...
I want to head home ...
to a wife 's embrace or a pet 's face .
Not waste my life ...
partying with you losers .
Not with me .
A good man ...
who went whoring with me last night .
Fooling around so soon ?
Here she comes .
Quiet .
What 's so funny ?
Nothing .
One last thing ...
One more glass !
What are we listening to ?
Don 't turn it off .
It 's beautiful .
You guys seem tight .
Do you meet often ?
What are you looking at ?
Beautiful you .
What a sap .
Are you hurt ?
Tun ...
Is she dead ?
Wait !
Drive away .
I said drive away !
Drive away !
Get closer , please .
Okay .
Big smile , Nuch .
Or you won 't look pretty .
All Science Majors ...
gather for a class photo .
They 're calling you .
Where 's Jane ?
Taking photos with her friends .
I thought maybe you broke up .
Come ! Let 's go .
I phoned but you didn 't pick up .
Was it on silent ?
Nuch asked about you today .
When will you be free ?
She wants to ...
Jane .
How can you act like this ?
Pretending nothing happened .
Since that night ...
I haven 't slept soundly .
I 'm upset as well .
At least we should have checked .
It was an accident .
That 's easy for you to say .
You weren 't behind the wheel ...
Hi , Ti . / Hey .
How 's business ?
With you here this early ...
business should be bad .
Are my prints ready ?
Yeah . Just a sec .
Here .
Is your processor broken ?
Let 's see .
The nerve .
Nice prints and you 're great .
If they suck it 's my fault .
Let 's check the negative .
No way .
I took them . I should know .
We 'll see .
See .
Your negatives are bad .
Tun .
Can you hear me ?
Help !
Don 't be scared . I 'm here now .
What 's wrong with your camera ?
I don 't know .
The whole roll is ruined .
That many ?
What are these shadows ?
My camera must be broken .
How should I tell Nuch ?
Tun ...
Look at this picture .
That woman ...
Do you think she 's dead ?
That 's enough .
I 'll have my camera fixed tomorrow .
Tun ...
Look at this picture .
Are you sure it was here ?
Excuse me .
What happened ?
A few days ago a car hit the billboard .
Must have been drunk .
Was anyone hurt ?
No .
Just the broken sign .
Are you sure ?
What ?
Nothing .
Thank you .
What ?
You sure you checked everywhere ?
Nothing .
Thanks anyways .
He called every precinct and hospital .
No accidents were reported that night .
That 's not possible .
What about the girl we hit ?
You sure he called every one ?
Maybe someone helped her .
Maybe she 's fine .
How could she be fine ?
We ploughed her down .
And even if she 's fine ...
Something is in those pictures .
I told you they 're not related to her .
They 're just bad exposures .
Get it ?
Tun ...
You need to make some merit .
These pictures ...
show that a spirit is haunting you .
How long have you been a photographer ?
Why are you showing me these ?
I know ...
But don 't you find these shadows strange ?
You want to see spirits ?
I 'll show you some .
Here .
Auntie Cham 's spirit .
You know where she is now ?
She 's selling grilled bananas next door .
Here 's Auntie Cham . And here .
All Auntie Cham .
Taken on the same day .
They 're just double exposures ...
and out of focus .
Come on . I know that .
Everyone is familiar with this place .
Just an ordinary location ...
that we pass ...
and see everyday .
Now look at these pictures ...
taken of the same place .
In these ...
the bridge looks nicer .
That means photography ...
does not reproduce reality .
It depends on how ...
the image is framed .
What is revealed .
What is concealed .
Your perspective is critical .
Special Scoop : Spirit Pictures
Jane , you 're early .
I 'll get it .
Hello ? / Hello , Tun .
It 's Jane . I 'll come by later .
Hello ?
Tun , can you hear me ?
Tun !
Hello ?
What 's wrong ?
I don 't know .
My neck 's hurt since the accident .
You should go see a doctor .
I 'm sure it 's not serious .
What 's the use of talking to these spoofs ?
Real Ghosts
Are you a reporter ?
No .
The funeral foundation sent us .
We run a legal operation .
We have all the right permits .
Excuse me .
Are all these pictures fakes ?
Piak ! Tell the boss he has guests .
Everyone fakes them .
You know ...
these photos are always a hit .
Any issue with them sells out .
But you think ...
we can always find real ones ?
Isn 't that deceiving the public ?
Our readers ...
want to see scary photos .
They don 't want love stories .
Does that mean every photo is fake ?
I didn 't say that .
Take a look .
See anything ?
This is the first photo I had .
I took it at home .
The shadow ...
bears a likeness to my mom .
Believe what you will .
But this picture ...
was taken after she passed away .
You know ...
sometimes ...
spirits long for their loved ones .
In my opinion ...
these pictures ...
represent more than ...
macabre urban legends .
They are signs .
Think about it .
Why would the dead ...
return to the living ...
without a message to convey ?
Most importantly ...
I believe ...
these shadows ...
are related to someone in the picture .
A father ...
mother ...
or lover .
Or someone ...
you maligned in life .
How can we tell if they 're real ...
and not fakes ?
What about polaroids ?
Can you fake them ?
You load the film and press the shutter .
The photo ejects .
Tell me then ...
How can they be faked ?
How do we know what they want ?
Perhaps ...
the answer is in the photo .
Two more poses .
Big smiles .
Let 's have a different pose .
Embrace her , hold the bouquet ...
and kiss her cheek .
Beautiful .
We 're done .
Thank you both .
Take them to the dressing room .
What the ...
Who 's doing that ?
Aum , check the fuse !
Hey ! Aum !
Who 's doing that ?
Is it you , Aum ?
Who is it ?
Who 's there !
I asked who it is !
Where are you , Aum ?
Who 's there !
Please step off the scale .
Step on it again .
Been working hard lately ?
Not really .
How long has it hurt ?
For quite awhile .
But it 's gotten worse lately .
I had a car accident .
An accident ?
Physically , you 're fine .
You shouldn 't worry .
But it really hurts .
Your x-rays are normal .
It may be a sprain .
Try the medicine I prescribed .
Mr. Tun , please pick up your prescription .
Take this medicine ...
3 times a day after meals ...
until the prescription runs out .
Lying bastard .
Pardon ?
Yes ?
Nothing .
Lying bastard .
As for this medicine ...
Sir !
What 's wrong ?
... is rarely seen .
When grasshoppers begin mating ...
the male smells the female ...
from a distance up to 100 meters .
The male carefully approaches the female .
It hooks itself onto her belly .
And they begin to mate .
The female 's response is surprising .
The male becomes her prey .
She slowly eats off his head ...
while they are mating .
Eventually ...
the male succumbs to death .
Excuse me , where is Room 301 ?
Jane .
Who 's there ?
Tonn ...
What 's wrong ?
Tun ...
I 'm going to die .
What 's going on ?
The photos ...
Bring me those photos .
What photos ?
Are you drunk ?
Those photos ...
Where did you hide them ?
Give them to me .
Remember that bitch .
Calm down .
What photos ?
Just give them to me !
Please calm down .
Tonn , calm down .
What photos ?
Tonn .
I 'll call your wife .
What are you doing ?
Cleaning up .
Your neck still sore ?
Yeah .
Take it easy . Don 't work so much .
Natrenapa Chan-ngam , Honor Society 1995
Tonn .
It 's Tun .
Are you home ?
Tonn .
Natrenapa Chan-ngam
Tonn !
I 'm really sorry .
Do you know ...
what was bothering him ?
No . Suddenly he ...
It 's your gang 's fault .
Have you all gone insane ?
What do you mean ?
You 've all committed suicide .
Who ?
Don 't you know ?
The other two ...
also killed themselves .
Which two ?
The two who sat next to you .
Who 's this woman ?
Where did you get that ?
She 's the shadow in the photos , right ?
Who is she ?
How is she related to you ?
I knew her in college .
Her name is Natre .
She was a quiet person ...
without any friends .
We all thought she was weird .
I felt sorry for her .
We dated but I kept it secret .
She loved me a lot .
She threatened to slit her wrists .
I didn 't know what to do .
My friends thought it was funny .
How were they involved ?
Why are they dead ?
They ...
What did they do ?
I don 't know .
Tonn said he 'd take care of it .
After that , Natre disappeared .
I never saw her again .
Didn 't you try to stop them ?
How could you let it happen ?
What could I do ?
Now everyone is dead .
I 'm ...
I 'm going to die next .
It 's funny how ...
we always say ...
if we could turn back time ...
we ...
we would reverse all our wrongs .
Do you think she 's okay ?
Will she be there ?
Go to sleep .
I 'll keep you company tonight .
Excuse me .
Do you have any toilet paper ?
Can I poo first ?
I 'm sorry .
What 's bothering you ?
What 's wrong ?
What is it ?
Is it around here ?
Excuse me .
Do you know where this is ?
Mom , where is this house ?
Ma 'am .
Excuse me ...
Is this Natre 's house ?
What do you want ?
Well ...
We 're her friends .
Natre 's friends ? Come inside .
Have some water . You must be tired .
Did you drive from Bangkok ?
Yes .
We 'd like to ask about Natre .
She 's not feeling well .
She 's taking a nap .
Should I wake her ?
Stay for dinner .
I was about to cook .
I 'm making her favorite dish .
Natre will be so happy .
Her friends don 't visit often .
Wait right here .
Where are you going ?
How dare you ?
Did she commit suicide ?
We should cremate her .
No .
I won 't cremate her .
Ma 'am ...
I don 't know if you believe such things ...
but I 'd like you to look at these photos .
They were taken around campus .
Some of the places ...
were rooms Natre had been in .
And these shadows appeared .
I think that ...
Natre 's spirit is restless .
Natre ...
My dear Natre .
Why don 't you visit me ?
Can you tell me what happened ?
Why she left Bangkok ?
Ma 'am ...
Ma 'am .
These shadows ...
might mean her spirit is not at peace .
We should hold her funeral .
Please .
When she came home ...
she seemed different .
She wouldn 't talk to anyone .
No one knows what happened in Bangkok .
Then she overdosed on pills .
Luckily , her mother found her ...
and got her to the hospital on time .
When she recovered ...
she climbed on the hospital roof ...
and jumped off the edge .
Why wouldn 't her mom cremate her ?
She 's been distraught ever since Natre 's death .
No matter what she refused to cremate her .
All the villagers were scared .
No one wanted to socialize with her .
Can 't sleep ?
Tell me the truth ...
Did you love Natre ?
I tried to ...
I believed that one day I would .
But I was fooling myself .
When I broke it off ...
I was a total asshole .
But she still loved me the same .
I want this to be over .
If she wants me to die I will .
Don 't say that .
It 's almost over .
No it 's not .
I know she 'll come for me .
Tun .
We 've come this far .
And you 're sorry for what you did .
I 'm sure she knows .
Don 't talk about death anymore .
I 'm sorry .
Do you still love me ?
No matter what you won 't leave me , right ?
Jane .
Tun ...
Jane ...
Where did you go ?
Why did you leave me alone ?
We 've got to leave .
Asshole !
Why did you leave me ?
Didn 't you love me ?
How could you leave me ?
Tun ...
Are you feeling better ?
What happened last night ?
Tun ...
Jane ...
The abbot said ...
Natre will be cremated today .
It 's over .
Hello . / Hello , Jane .
Picking up photos ?
Where 's Tun ?
He 's busy .
Good .
When he 's busy ...
I get to see you .
You went on vacation ?
To the beach .
When did you go ?
Last week .
This photo is ...
What 's wrong ?
You look fatter .
I didn 't recognize you .
Hi .
Jumbo prints .
Write your name , please .
Get her guys !
Jane ...
Why are you crying ?
Asshole ...
How could you be so cruel ?
Where did you find these ?
If I didn 't find them ...
I 'd be a fool forever , right ?
Let me explain .
What 's there to say ?
I always believed you .
I thought I knew you .
Tun .
Take her picture ...
so she doesn 't blab .
Tun , help me .
I know it was wrong .
Take her picture now !
What 's wrong !
I 'm your buddy !
Hurry !
Tun , help me .
I never forgave myself .
But I was young and stupid .
I 've heard enough .
I 'm going home .
Come on out !
Where are you ?
I thought you loved me !
Loved me so much !
Till death do us part !
She 's gone now .
Sometimes ...
spirits long for their loved ones .
... I Hope You Enjoyed ! ... " Encoded By TuGAZx " " PTpOWeR "